[She's Wild Fire]
[Episode 15: Until You Care]
[Shencheng First Garment Factory]
Ms. Xie,
these are our imported,
fully automatic sewing machines.
They're three times
more efficient than manual labor.
And the stitches are even smoother
than handmade ones.
Many big factories in Shencheng
are fighting to order them.
Mr. Chen said
if you have time,
please do meet with him.
Alright.
I will meet with him when I'm free.
Great!
Ladies,
welcome here today.
It's going to be hard work from now on.
Just put your heart into it
and teach them well,
alright?
Instead of running the business,
why bring in a bunch of old ladies?
What are they trying to pull?
The factory renovation is almost done.
What's the plan next?
I found several excellent seamstresses,
and a professor who returned
from studying abroad.
I plan to
combine theory and practice,
and train our own female workers hands-on.
Well said.
Even the best machines
will become obsolete one day,
but people are different.
People
will keep growing
if they're willing to learn.
Machines can never replace that.
But then again,
people
are uncontrollable.
If we work hard to train them,
and they get poached later,
this business deal won't be worth it.
Isn't that a good thing?
I train them
not just for Blooming Path,
but in the hopes
that no matter where they go,
they can make a living.
They won't need to depend on anyone,
or act on anyone's whims.
How wonderful is that?
Chang Yongbin has been tailing you lately.
I'm worried for your safety.
I'll ask Biao...
It's fine.
No need.
Hello, Mr. Chen,
it's Xie Nanfeng.
I'm free tomorrow.
How about we meet in person?
I'll take all the machines you have.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Mr. Chu,
play along with me tomorrow.
Sure.
What's my reward?
What reward do you want?
I want...
One kiss is enough?
What do you say?
Ms. Xie,
are you really buying
all 70 of our imported sewing machines?
Of course.
Blooming Path is
expanding production capacity.
Your machines
will only be put to good use in my hands.
So about the price...
You name the price.
You can spend my money
however you want.
That's great!
I'll prepare the contract right away.
I'll send it over
first thing tomorrow morning.
Your acting has improved,
Mr. Chu.
Being nice to you
is never an act.
Sir,
are you short on cash?
Da Li Lai Loan Company
not only issues loans fast,
but the interest rates are negotiable too.
How much can you lend?
That depends on you.
How much do you want?
How much did he ask for?
Half a million.
Give him one million.
You know what?
Our female workers have already started.
And they're working
while training.
They're all very enthusiastic.
That's great.
Aren't you curious
who I lent the money to?
Got it.
You have so many business dealings.
There's no need to ask about all of them.
Xie Nanfeng,
you really don't care at all, do you?
What am I supposed to care about?
Care about what I do.
Care about me.
Are you really not the least bit
possessive of me?
Why should I be possessive?
You're not my personal property.
What about now?
Do you care about me a little more?
Then I'll stay right here today
until you care about me.
Xie Nanfeng!
We just got out of the red,
and you blow it on a new factory?
Who agreed to this?
Sitting on inventory instead of moving it,
and buying used machines?
You're not here to run a business.
You're here to sabotage it.
I propose
we dismiss Xie Nanfeng as General Manager,
before she drags us all
into the fire.
Are you done?
All risks from Ms. Xie's decisions
will be borne entirely by me.
If her decisions
cause you any losses,
I will buy all your shares
at three times the original stock price.
If there are no further objections,
the meeting continues.
Fine.
We're willing to bet
on Ms. Xie's decisions,
but we can't
sit on cash instead of expanding
and grabbing orders,
only to blow it all on female workers
and build women's bathrooms!
We barely have any orders,
yet we're running three shifts
and even giving menstrual leave!
Is this running a factory
or running a charity?
Do you have any idea how long
a woman's bra actually lasts?
Bras are not fast-moving consumer goods.
One can be worn for over half a year.
Once the initial hype dies down,
the market will saturate in no time.
There won't be any greater demand.
If you don't make bras,
you can pivot to something else.
We can't keep burning money like this.
No rush.
What's the hurry?
In a couple of days,
the answer will reveal itself.
Well, look who it is!
If it isn't Ms. Xie!
What brings you
to my humble establishment?
Wait.
Let me guess.
Is it because all the orders
ran over to my side,
and you're feeling a bit uneasy?
Exactly!
I heard Manager Chang
bought some imported Japanese machines.
I had to learn from you.
Speaking of which, I have to thank you.
If you hadn't generously backed out,
how would I have gotten these machines
for just an extra 300,000?
You have no idea.
These machines in my factory
work day and night,
non-stop.
My hands are cramped from taking orders!
Another call!
Speak of the devil.
So busy!
You want to increase your order volume?
No problem.
Nobody's buying?